The second half of the season has started!
The second half has started!
Yes, this is the CJB lead, the lead ceremony number 12, Yamanashi Nakayashiko!
I'm Riko Ueda, from the Battenshan Group.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Rikuchan in the first half.
And Rik-chan
Yes, I've been asked to call you
Yes, please do this.
Now, you all can now comment on this.
Please call me
Yes, please.
The second half of the round is a question that we want to ask each other
I'm going to start with me.
Okay, I'll go first.
I'll start with you.
Let's see, Fukuoka, isn't it?
Fukuoka
When I went to Fukuoka and Anzai, we all went out for dinner after the concert.
Afterwards, we often go to a café with the members.
We often go to a café.
Do you have any recommendations for places to eat?
I'm already over 20 years old.
I see... And alcohol?
Do you drink?
Yes, I do.
I'm a member of the club.
I do.
I see.
Wow.
But what do you usually go out to eat?
Last time I was in Fukuoka for the spring tour.
I went to Fukuoka
We all went to a cafe at night
We went to a cafe at night.
We had motsu nabe for dinner.
Tororo nabe (grated yam in hot pot) for dinner
Tororonabe.
I've never heard of Tororonabe.
It's not from Fukuoka?
I wonder if it's from Fukuoka
Tororonabe or curry nabe
Curry nabe?
Isn't there curry nabe in Tokyo?
Uh, there might be.
There might be.
I've never had it.
But it's really good.
I always go for the yam hot pot.
I really want to try morotonabe.
I don't like it.
There are some members who can't eat it.
So we have mizutaki.
Most of the time.
Have you ever tried cod roe?
I see it all the time.
Mentaiko in a bento box.
That's right.
Everyone eats it.
They eat it.
I've seen you eat it.
I've never had it either.
I've never had it.
It's true, I've never had my own.
But I've always wanted to try it.
I've been looking at it.
When you say you have a recommendation, I often do.
Uh...
Can you eat motsu nabe?
I love it... so much.
I love it so much, but...
I can't usually eat motsu nabe.
But if it's motsunabe...
I want you to eat it with yuzu kosho.
Yuzu kosho!
What's this?
Is this only in Fukuoka?
I'm crazy about it.
Yuzu kosho for sure!
Hee...
So before...
Echigo-ya, a motsunabe restaurant
I introduced it on my blog a while back.
but they have miso and akumyo.
Shiro-miso (white miso) and Akumyo (akumyo).
and so on.
So if you can go there for a while
I'll be there when I can.
I hope you can go there.
I hope you'll go there.
And the ramen...And the ramen.
I'm sure there's a lot of places
A lot of them.
There are places where you can eat for as little as 300 yen.
And then there's Shinshin.
There are so many places in line.
I hope you'll come this time!
It's ramen after the concert!
Ramen and rice!
Main course!
and eat
While eating ramen
and drink some alcohol.
And at the end of the show
The end of the concert.
If you're going to the show the day before, you have to go to the show the next day, so...
So after the show... after the show...
I said, "Good work.
That's so nice.
Do you want a drink?
I'll have a drink.
I do, but not that much.
Even the members...
Four of us can drink now.
But we don't go out for drinks.
I haven't said a word about it.
So...
So, when you're in Fukuoka...
I'll ask him to call you.
I will.
I'll see you later.
We didn't exchange numbers, did we?
I didn't know.
Of course you don't.
Then I'll definitely get you on that.
Thank you.
Sake.
But it's really a place where you can drink a lot of alcohol.
Fukuoka
Kyushu is the best place to drink!
The food is delicious!
While eating rice.
That's why
I haven't had that many drinks yet.
I haven't been out drinking that much yet, so
I'll recommend a place
I'll send it to you as soon as I remember
I'll send it to you like a memo.
Please go with me.
I'll come with you.
Yes, please.
I'll be there.
Before the concert.
It's funny to say this, but...
I was so nervous.
Really?
And the other day...
I had my first live performance.
I don't know what I was nervous about.
I don't know what I'm nervous about, but that day I really...
I only had two bites.
There were two parts to the show.
I was able to get through both parts.
I wasn't even hungry.
I was so nervous.
I was so nervous that when I came out
When I came out of the door
I'm nervous.
I get nervous too.
But lately, I don't get nervous at shows.
How do you cope with it?
Coping?
But before an Ebituju concert...
I have a meditation time.
And after that, Nakayama time.
Nakayama time?
That's amazing!
It's pretty chaotic before a show, isn't it?
I go on stage as it is.
That really happens a lot.
That's why we have a time to make up our minds.
I'm going to concentrate for about a minute.
After that, you might be more concerned about the Nakayama time.
You might be worried about that?
Are you okay?
After that, I'll go backstage.
Nakayama time?
After you've settled down for meditation...
I'm going to go on stage.
I'm going to go on stage.Bringing it to a sense of tension.
I had my Nakayama time.
Kuru-kuru-kuru-kuru-kuru-kuru with everyone
Kuru-kuru-kuru-kuru-kuru from the opposite side
Float your body vertically vertically
Finally, we jumped up and down 5 times.
And then go up on the stage.
Wow!
And Tadan is leading the way.
It's true, I've seen them perform live.
It's different from what I'm feeling now.
It's so powerful.
I wondered where it came from.
Oh...
I'm pretty much just going up like that.
Ai Kiyoyama, a member of the group...
She's really like Tachidan.
She sometimes goes berserk like what's wrong with her.
Ai!
At a live performance.
That's why I want that switch
I want it.
Ah!
I saw it naturally.
It's so natural.
Leader.
I mean...
I talk to him a lot at shows.
Lately...
I've been thinking
Because we're a group.
I have to be aware of what's going on around me
I have to be aware of what's going on around me, but...
But I'm a girl who concentrates on herself.
Heh.
She's also concerned about her surroundings.
You're the one who's making it together.
She focuses on herself the most.
Ah.
So don't be nervous.
Oh, I see.
I'll say it.
It's true, we have a new member.
On stage.
I've been thinking about it.
I wonder if I can do this next one.
"I have to do this for the next song.
I think about it a lot.
We're going to have our 8th anniversary show soon.
At that time...
I'll just focus on myself.
But I have to eat before the show.
I know.
No, of course not.
But until a while ago, I ate too much.
I'd lose energy quickly.
It's better if you don't eat.
It's better to not eat.
But I thought two bites were a little too little for me.
I've been eating four bowls of white rice
I eat four bowls of white rice.
Four bowls?
That's right.
Does it move your body?
But I have time for Nakayama.
Then eat four bowls of rice.
Make it Ueda time.
Facial muscles.
It's nice, isn't it?
We move our facial muscles.
I'm doing it.
I refer to that a lot.
Nakayama time
I'm copying you.
And Rikuchan time.
I don't like it myself, don't you think?
Suddenly, he's in front of the stage.
I'm sorry, I'm going to start RICH-chan time.
People might get nervous.
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
There's a thing called Nakayama time in the EBITS schedule.
Nakayama time
Rehearsal
It's like Nakayama Time.
There's a time...
Cute Iricchan time
I think it should be called "Marichan Time".
That's true.
But I think I'm a little more enthusiastic about Nakayama Time.But I'm a little more enthusiastic about the Nakayama time.
I have a feeling
Nakayama time and Torichan time
That's exactly what the group
We're both new members
join the group
We're not too old.
I was the youngest to start with.
But even then...
I was the youngest.
Seven years apart.
I'm just now
with the youngest
7 years old
Mie and Yuna are
the same age
First year in high school
So
how did they do?
From the youngest to the youngest
And then the juniors come in.
I got used to it.
At first, I didn't know
I didn't know what to do.
I was a trainer.
Let me do it
I didn't really know how to teach.
I really didn't know.
I didn't end up
I didn't really get much done.
But
It's hard.
I'm the second from the top
I was second from the top
of the group.
There's not a lot I can say about that yet.
But...
I'm still the youngest
It's very difficult to be the youngest and then the youngest
I think it must be very difficult
I'm sure it's very difficult.
But I've seen videos of the audition period
videos of the audition period
I was always looking at the other person
and see if it's easy to understand.
I thought it would be easier to understand if I did it this way.
I used that as a reference.
Do you talk a lot?
With the youngest girl.
I got to talk a lot.
At first
I had an image of her as a quiet, calm person.
But lately she's been pretty good.
Even during live performances
Even during a live show.
I've heard that she's always coming right up to me or something.
That's nice.
But the other day, for the first time...
I heard you're in love.
I see.
That's what we're going to do.
For us, too.
We'll be able to go back to the way we felt the first time.
together.
It's so fresh and fun.
I'm trying to tell you something.
How do you tell them?
Younger members
I'm really confused about this.
When I say it, love...
I sound soft when I say it.
but when I say it, it can sound stern.
but when I say it, I think it can sound a bit harsh.
I'm basically a little bit
I try to be a little bit conscious of what is normal
But I ask other members to follow up
I often ask other members to follow up
I often ask other members to follow up.
If I do it a little too strongly
I'll ask Ai and the others to follow up gently
to follow up with me.
I'll be
I'm too strict.
I can't say much, can I?
Kaho, who's the same age as me...
She tells me a lot.
I don't know how to tell her.
I don't know how to tell them.
I don't know how they feel about it.I don't know how they feel about it.
I don't know what they think.
I'll think, "That was harsh.
I can't say it.
And even if I wanted to say something, I just said it.
I'll hold it in for now.
And I wonder if it's really not a good idea.
Ebitu-chan is
You're more skilled than me.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not.
How do you communicate that to them?
I wonder how she's pulling them up? I'm just wondering.
It feels so good.
It's so hard.
Rika, the top one.
Mayama.
She's been doing a lot lately.
She's been pulling us all along.
Watching and learning from them
I'm learning from her.
While I'm learning
I'd like to see
I'd like to see what you're doing.
Referring to the video
I'd like to do my best.
I'm so serious.
I'm so serious at the end.
But you know what?
I'm going to introduce Rikuchan time
Hibi live performance
I'll do my best to make a live show like Ebitu-chan's.
I'll do my best to make it like Ebitu-chan's live.
Thank you very much.
Today, it looks like Lapuencel.
Lapuencel?
I don't know what he said.
Who is it? They said something.
She's my favorite princess with the haircut,
I thought it looked like her,
I thought it would be a little weird to say it out of the blue,
I'm glad. I was surprised.
I'll give it some time,
After some time, I finally said it.
I said it.
Thank you very much.
Let's do it again.
Let's take pictures every time.
Please take a picture too.
I'd love to.